Rating sector's Crisil Share Company has
announced a dividend of ₹ per share to investors and Rekha
Jhunjhunwala also has a big investment in this company and
currently this company is completely debt
free. Information about Crisil Share Company
Crisil Limited, which is a leading rating
company, under which the company also works in Bond Rating,
Bank Loan Rating, SM Rating,
Infrastructure Advisory. The
company has succeeded in expanding its business in
India including United States, United Kingdom,
Argentina, Poland, Chi, Singapore and UAE. The
company is completely
debt free. The company is currently completely
debt free and the company has a
free cash flow of Rs 108.5 crore. The
promoter's holding is recorded at 66.65%. The
total market cap of the company is Rs 36654.64
crore. Return of 64% in the last one year. The
profit growth of the company is
58% in the last 3 years and revenue growth is
recorded at 2.36%. Along with this, the company has given a
return of 37% in the last 3 years and
in the last 1 year  Jhunjhunwala has given a return of 64% and
bought a share of 5.47%.
After the demise of Rakesh Jhunjhunwala, his wife Rekha Jhunjhunwala
is handling the portfolio, so his total
net worth is currently
43.7 crores. He has bought a share
of 5.47% in Chrysal Share Company in December 2022,
whose current
value is 22.4 crores.
In 2023, the stock gave dividend four times. In the year 2023,
Chrysal Share had given dividend four times. In
that, the first dividend was of ₹ in March 2023,
after that in May 2023, a dividend of ₹ was given, then
in August 2023 a dividend of ₹ was given and in November 2023 a
dividend of ₹ was given. The company has
announced to give a dividend of 8 per share. Currently, the
dividend of Chrysal Share Company
is 1.08%, which is quite good and now the company has given a dividend of
88 per share.  Share dividend has been
announced and its ex-date has been kept as March 28,
2024, hence the record date has been fixed as
April 1, 2024. Disclaimer: The
vision of Equity News is to promote financial literacy in India. The
content we
post is purely for educational
and entertainment purposes. We are also
not registered financial advisors and hence
we do not provide any investment or financial advisory services.
You will be solely responsible for your money and
your decisions.
Please consult any registered financial advisor for your financial investments.